export default[
    {
        id:1,
        question:"How many ghosts visit Mr. Scrooge in the book, 'A Christmas Carol' by Charles Dickens?", 
        a:"2",
        b:"3",
        c:"4",
        d:"5 or more",
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:"What movie is the expression 'I see dead people' from?", 
        a:"The Shining",
        b:"It",
        c:"The Sixth Sense",
        d:"Clockwork Orange",
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:"What is Batman's name?", 
        a:"Bruce Wayne",
        b:"Bryce Wayne",
        c:"John Wayne",
        d:"Charlie Wayne",
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:"What was the name of the tow truck in 'Cars' the movie?", 
        a:"Guido",
        b:"Tow Mater",
        c:"Tow Truck",
        d:"Doc",
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:"In the movie 'Finding Nemo', where was Nemo taken?", 
        a:"Melbourne, Australia",
        b:"Canberra, Australia",
        c:"Perth, Australia",
        d:"Sydney, Australia",
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:"Where did Harry Potter go to school?", 
        a:"Hogwarts",
        b:"Gryffindor",
        c:"Hogsmeade",
        d:"Oxford",
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:"What type of monster is Shrek?", 
        a:"Dwarf",
        b:"Ogre",
        c:"Giant",
        d:"Elf",
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:"What is the name of Japanese cartoons?", 
        a:"Cartoons",
        b:"Manga",
        c:"Anime",
        d:"Shounen",
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:"What hero in DC universe is very similar to the Greek God Poseidon?", 
        a:"Batman",
        b:"Green Lantern",
        c:"Aqua Man",
        d:"Superman",
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:"What color is the road that Dorothy follows in the Wizard of Oz?", 
        a:"Yellow",
        b:"Red",
        c:"Orange",
        d:"Black",
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        id:11,
        question:"What genre of music is 'The Weeknd' best known for?", 
        a:"Rap",
        b:"Pop",
        c:"R&B",
        d:"EDM",
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        id:12,
        question:"What does the term 'NFL' stand for?", 
        a:"National Foosball League",
        b:"National Football League",
        c:"Natural Forest Land",
        d:"Nested For Loop",
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        id:13,
        question:"What social media platform uses a bird as it's logo?", 
        a:"Instagram",
        b:"Facebook",
        c:"Tik Tok",
        d:"Twitter",
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        id:14,
        question:"What music artist goes by the name Ye?", 
        a:"Kendrick Lamar",
        b:"Eminem",
        c:"Kanye West",
        d:"Yeat",
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        id:15,
        question:"What video game franchise has a vehicle called a Banshee?", 
        a:"Halo",
        b:"Call of Duty",
        c:"Star Wars Battlefront",
        d:"God of War",
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        id:16,
        question:"Who was the actor who played as Forrest Gump in the movie, 'Forrest Gump'?", 
        a:"Tom Cruise",
        b:"Tom Holland",
        c:"Tom Hiddleston",
        d:"Tom Hanks",
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        id:17,
        question:"What movie is the Netflix series, 'Cobra Kai', a sequel of?", 
        a:"Snakes on A Plane",
        b:"Karate Kid",
        c:"Saving Private Ryan",
        d:"Fight Club",
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        id:18,
        question:"Which music legend wrote the song, 'Tangled Up in Blue'?", 
        a:"Bob Dylan",
        b:"John Lennon",
        c:"Queen",
        d:"Elton John",
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        id:19,
        question:"What state was most of the show, 'The Walking Dead', filmed?", 
        a:"Alabama",
        b:"California",
        c:"Georgia",
        d:"Florida",
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        id:20,
        question:"What sport does Lebron James play?", 
        a:"Hockey",
        b:"Basketball",
        c:"Football",
        d:"Soccer",
        correctAnswer: "b"
    }
    
]